JONATHAN RHYMES

Software Engineer

jonrhymes@gmail.com

(407) 489-8643 ST. PETERSBURG, FL

<u>LinkedIn</u> - <u>Heroku</u> - <u>Github</u>

SUMMARY

Software Engineer with an eye for design and details who creates applications that inspire and excite users. My experience as a TV and film editor instilled in me a passion for artistic collaboration and seeing a project to fruition in the most engaging way

SKILLS

Full-Stack, Front-End, Back-End, Web development, React.js, Express, NodeJS, MongoDB, Mongoose, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SASS, JSON, AJAX, Python, jQuery, Flexbox, Bootstrap, Git, Github, heroku, Adobe Photoshop, API, UI / UX

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly, New York — Software Engineering Fellow

APRIL 2020 - JULY 2020

- Designed full-stack applications: Card Game
- Used experience as graphic designer: Springs app
- Collaborated with other engineers: Shipping API app

Anomaly Entertainment, New York — Film & TV Editor

MAY 2018 - APRIL 2020

- Administered project management, organization & workflow best practices
- Designed graphics using Adobe Photoshop and After Effects

EDUCATION

General Assembly, New York — Software Engineering Immersive Remote

APRIL 2020 - JULY 2020

University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia — B.A. English, Cinema Studies

AUGUST 2003 - MAY 2006